branoo.com 2014-09-22

# Branoo

We value the trust you place in us. That's why we insist upon the highest standards for secure customer information privacy. Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices.

Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically.

By visiting this Website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our Website.

By mere use of the Website, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Use.

  1. Collection of personal identifiable information and other information: When you use our Website, we collect and store your personal information which is provided by you from time to time. Our primary goal in doing so is to provide you a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our Website to make your experience safer and easier. More importantly, while doing so we collect personal information from you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose. In general, you can browse the Website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature on the Website.
  2. Purpose of personal data collection: We use personal information to provide the services you request. We use your personal information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, help promote a safe service, collect money, measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience, detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity, enforce our terms and conditions and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.
  3. Disclose personal information: We will not disclose any personal information to third parties.
  4. Accessing and modifying personal information: Register user can access account & modify/ change data by signing in his/her account.
